fyffest.com 2019-07-30

# GOLDENVOICE PRIVACY POLICY | Goldenvoice

### General Overview

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.

Goldenvoice is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process and complete the commercial transactions you request, and to provide you with a more personalized experience on our site. We have created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of all of our customers and visitors. The following Privacy Policy discloses the information-gathering and dissemination practices and policies of Goldenvoice.

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. For some services, we either collect and transfer personal information to a service provider, or you may visit other merchants through links on our site who may collect and use your personal information. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others.

Please read the following to learn more about our data collection policies and practices.

  1. Types of Information that may be collected.
  2. How is information collected?
  3. How we use the information we collect.
  4. With whom the information may be disclosed.
  5. What choices do I have about Goldenvoice collecting, using, and disclosing my information?
  6. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?
  7. Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards.
  8. Links to other Websites.
  9. A special note for parents concerning privacy.
  10. International users.
  11. Limitation of Liability.
  12. Notification of changes and acceptance of the Privacy Policy.
  13. Correcting and updating personal information.
  14. Opting out of Registration.
  15. Whom do I contact with questions or concerns about this privacy policy?

### 1\. Types of information that may be collected

The personally identifiable information we collect is used to facilitate delivery of tickets and/or other products and/or services to our customers. In the process of providing these products and/or services, we require our customers to provide certain personally identifiable information. Specific details may include, but are not limited to the following and may be subject to change:

In the case of contests, promotions, and/or newsletter registrations or other features that may or may not involve a purchase: We may require all users and/or customers wishing to participate in any of our contests, drawings, sweepstakes, promotions, newsletters, Fantasy Games, Webcasts or other interactive features which may or may not require a purchase to complete an entry form which will require the submission of certain personally-identifiable information.

The personally-identifiable information that may be collected in an entry form includes, but may not be limited to: customer’s first name, last name, zip code, phone number, age and email address. Winners of contests, drawings, sweepstakes, and/or promotions will be required to provide additional personally identifiable information such as a shipping address and telephone number. If the privacy policy varies for a particular sweepstakes or promotion, that information will be disclosed in the sweepstakes or promotion rules.

In the case of a ticket or other product and/or service which involves a purchase on our Site: In order to complete the purchase of a product and/or service, an online credit card transaction is required. During this process we generate and collect certain personally identifiable information.

The personally identifiable information that may be collected from our customers in completion of a product and/or service purchase, includes, but may not be limited to: customer’s first and last name, first and last name of the credit card owner, credit card billing address, credit card number, credit card security code, credit card expiration date, customer’s shipping address, phone number, and email address. You may also have the opportunity to permit us to maintain this information in a personal profile for you so you do not have to re-enter the information each time you make a purchase.

If a customer sends us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to such customer.

Back to Top

### 2\. How is information collected?

We may collect information from you in several different areas on our Site, including but not limited to those described below:

**Registration**

You may be asked first to complete a registration form and provide personally-identifiable information. You may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features our Site may choose to offer, including, but not limited to, newsletters, contests, forums, fantasy, webcasts or other subscription based services.

**Newsletters and Site Emails**

We may offer free newsletters to share information with you about our Site, about us and our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our business partners and advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on our Site. You may cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided on our Site or in the designated area of the newsletters or emails.

**Contests or Sweepstakes**

We may operate contests and sweepstakes through our Site, which may require registration. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes. Your entry in the contest or sweepstakes may also result in your being added to our mailing lists as well as those of our promotional partners associated with the contest or sweepstakes. Acceptance of a prize may require you (unless prohibited by law) to allow us to post publicly some of your information on our Site, such as on a winner’s page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. In some instances, a third-party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on our Site, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we have no control over the information collected and accordingly urge you to review the official rules of the contest/sweepstakes as well as the advertiser’s or sponsor’s privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.

**Surveys or Voting**

From time-to-time we may request personally-identifiable information from you via surveys or voting polls. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information. At times, you may have to register to vote or to take part in a survey.

**Cookies**

As with many Websites, our Site uses standard technology called “cookies,” which are small data files that are transferred to your computer when you allow your browser to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your Web browser to our Site whenever you visit our Site, and make using our Site easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences. By tracking how and when you use our Site, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Site are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on our Site. Cookies may also allow our Site to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you generally can opt out of providing this information by turning the cookies off in your browser; however, some areas of our Site may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.

**IP Addresses and Click-stream Data**

We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data for purposes of system administration, to improve our Site and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors or other internal uses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. Our computers identify your computer by its IP address. When you request Web pages from our Site, our computers log your IP address.

Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from our Site. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at our Site, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

**Transaction Information**

If you place an order or subscribe for any of the services offered on our Site, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including financial information such as a credit card number and expiration date and general contact, billing and shipping information. We will use this information to complete the transaction that you have requested, e.g., to deliver the information, products or other services that you order, and to invoice you. Such information is collected and stored through encrypted means for your protection.

**Fantasy Games**

When you register to play Fantasy games, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information.

Back to Top

### 3\. How we use the information we collect?

We internally use personally identifiable information about our customers to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site’s content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our Site and provide better service to our customers.

We may use a customer’s email address and, in rare situations mailing address or phone number, to contact a customer regarding, administrative matters or notices, satisfaction with our Site and/or services and to provide further information regarding additional events, products or services we believe the customer would be interested in.

We may use information in the file we maintain about a customer to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems.

Back to Top

### 4\. With whom the information may be disclosed.

In order to process your requests we may provide your personally-identifiable information to service providers or other companies who work on our behalf in order, for example, to process the transaction and deliver the tickets or other goods or services you have ordered. When we do so, we use reasonable efforts to assure that they comply with our privacy policy and applicable law. Information we collect may be accessed by a variety of parties, depending upon the purpose for which the information was provided, and the context in which the information was provided.

If you purchase a ticket to a specific event on our Site, your first name, last name, physical address, phone number and email address may be provided to the management of the artist(s) for that event.

While we believe any disclosure of your information will result in opportunities that may be of interest to you, you have the right to opt out from receiving any future communications by contacting such third party directly. You may also opt out from receiving future communications from Goldenvoice through one of the following methods: (i) clicking on the appropriate links contained in our email communications; (ii) sending us a written request to the following address: Privacy Policy – Goldenvoice, C/O AEG Digital, 800 West Olympic Blvd., Suite 305, Los Angeles, CA 90015 or (iii) emailing: privacypolicy@aegworldwide.com

Your request must include your name, email address, mailing address and must be signed. (Signature only required for written request sent by regular mail). Please allow six weeks to process your request. You may also opt out by clicking on the appropriate links contained in our email communications. Under some circumstances, such as where we are contractually required to disclose ticket purchase information to artist management, we may not be able to fulfill your ticket order if you have requested that we do not disclose your information to third parties.

In addition, in the event that we go through an existing or potential business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, liquidation or sale of all or a portion of its assets, visitor information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

Finally, we may, without your consent, access and disclose your personal information, any communications sent or received by you, and any other information that we may have about you as may be permitted or required by law, regulation, rule or court order; pursuant to requests from governmental, regulatory or administrative agencies or law enforcement authorities; or to prevent, investigate, identify persons or organizations potentially involved in, or take any action regarding suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Service, or activity that appears to us to be illegal or we believe may expose us to legal liability. Additionally, we may disclose personal information in situations that we believe to be emergencies involving potential threats to the physical safety or any person or property if we believe that your information in any way relates to that threat.

Back to Top

### 5\. What choices do I have about Goldenvoice collecting, using, and disclosing my information?

It is possible for you to use much of our Site without giving us any personally identifiable information. When you do register with us or give us personally identifiable information, you will have an opportunity at the time we collect your information — to limit e-mail communications from Goldenvoice and from our third-party partners. You can request at any time that Goldenvoice not send future e-mail to you either by unsubscribing from the communication or by contacting us at privacypolicy@aegworldwide.com. Also, as mentioned above, there are ways to limit the information collected through technology — though some of our Site features won’t work if you decide to do this.

Even if you request that we not disclose your personal information to third parties, we may disclose personally identifiable information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Goldenvoice, Site users or the public. Information collected through this Site, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets or acquisition.

Back to Top

### 6\. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?

We have implemented reasonable security measures to safeguard your personally identifiable information using reasonable industry standards. However, please keep in mind that “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet and/or the World Wide Web.

Back to Top

### 7\. Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards

Our Site may make chat rooms, forums, webcasts and message boards available to its users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. We strongly recommend that you do not use your personal information as your user name or that you post any personally identifiable information on line, since such information will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. Goldenvoice cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, webcast, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy.

Back to Top

### 8\. Links to other Websites

You should be aware that when you are on our Site you could be directed to other sites beyond our control. For example, if you seek to purchase a ticket to a concert that is not sold on our Site or “click” on a banner advertisement, the “click” may take you off our Site onto a different Website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use our Site’s logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other Websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a Website that is linked to our Site, you should review that site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you submit to third-party Websites, including, without limitation, any Websites that may be connected to our Site by hypertext link or otherwise.

Back to Top

### 9\. A special note for parents concerning privacy

This Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children.

Back to Top

### 10\. International users.

If you are accessing this Site from outside of the United States, your information will be transferred to the United States. Regardless of where your information is collected or transferred, the information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Back to Top

### 11\. Limitation of Liability

By providing us with any personal information you expressly and unconditionally release and hold harmless Anschutz Entertainment Group, Inc., its parents, shareholders, owners, members, and each of their subsidiaries, affiliates, directors, officers, employees and agents (collectively, the “Releasees”) from any and all liability for any injuries, loss or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with the use and/or misuse of your collected personal information. In addition, while Goldenvoice takes efforts to ensure the proper and appropriate use of Goldenvoice data provided by Goldenvoice to third party companies, promotional partners or vendors, the Releasees are not liable for any injuries, loss or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with the use and/or misuse of your collected personal information by such third parties.

Back to Top

### 12\. Notification of changes and acceptance of the Privacy Policy

By using this Site, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. Goldenvoice may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, any such changes will be posted on this page, so that Goldenvoice may keep its users informed of its information collection practices. Accordingly, we recommend that you consult this page frequently so that you are aware of our latest policy and/or any changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Site shall constitute your acceptance of any such new or revised privacy policy. If at any point we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will send such person an email notifying him/her of such changes and giving him/her the option as to whether to allow us to use such information in such different manner. Without such consent, we will use personal information in accordance with the privacy policy under which it was collected.

Back to Top

### 13\. Correcting and updating personal information

If your PII changes, or if you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you should make changes to your password protected registered user profile on the Site, respond to an opt-out message in an email or text, or email us at privacypolicy@aegworldwide.com. Please note that to the extent that such information is stored in our databases, we will respond to your changes as soon as reasonably practicable, however that information may remain stored indefinitely in our back-up and archival records. Any information that is stored in aggregate (“headless”) form that may have been excerpted from is not considered PII and will not be updated or changed pursuant to a request from you.

Back to Top

### 14\. Opting out of Registration.

If you are a registered subscriber and no longer wish to receive our email communications, you may opt out. Choosing to opt out means we will remove your personal data from our database and you will not receive further communications from us. You may opt out by utilizing one of the following methods: (i) emailing us at privacypolicy@aegworldwide.com, (ii) using an option out message contained in an email from us, or (iii) calling us at 888-929-7849.

Back to Top

### 15\. Whom do I contact with questions or concerns about this privacy policy?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact Goldenvoice by sending a letter to:

Privacy Policy – Goldenvoice  
C/O AEG Digital  
800 West Olympic Blvd., Suite 305  
Los Angeles, CA 90015

You may also contact us by e-mail at: privacypolicy@aegworldwide.com

Back to Top
